Guide to the W. W. Morgan Papers circa 1905-1990
University of Chicago Library
- Series II: Correspondence
  - Cruikshank-Kuiper, 1975-1982 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Dreiser Richard D., 1983 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - D-E-F, 1952-1953 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Eaton Joel A., 1975-1978 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Edmondson Frank K., 1974-1982 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Edmondson Frank K., Correspondence, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Frost Edwin, 1922-1924 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Garrison Correspondence, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Gingerich Owen J.: The Discovery of the Spiral Arms of the Milky Way, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Gingerich, Owen J., 1982-1983 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Golay M., 1975-1979 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - G-H-I, 1952-1953 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Harper D.A., 1982 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Harper, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Hauck B., 1981 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Hearnshaw, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Herbig George H., 1974-1982 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Hoag Arthur A., 1975 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Hoffleit Dorrit, 1980-1982 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Hoffleit Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Humphreys Roberta M., 1975-1982 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Hynek J. Allen, 1972-1974 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - IAU Te Wandelen Guieren, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - The Institute for Advanced Study, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Intimate Letters from Helen to W.W. Morgan, 1952-1953 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Jaschek Carlos, 1975-1982 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Johnson Correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Jury Duty Correspondence, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - J-K-L, 1952-1953 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Kayser Susan, 1974-1980 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Keenan Phillip C., 1947-1948 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Keenan Phillip C., 1949-1951 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Keenan Phillip C., Correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Keenan Phillip C., Folder 1, 1979-1987 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Keenan Phillip C., Folder 2, 1979-1987 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Kluyver Helen, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Kotanyi C., 1982 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Kuiper Gerard P., Memorial, 1973-1975 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Kuiper Gerard P., Correspondence, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Landolt Arlo U., 1977 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence with Leiden, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Letters to Keep Forever, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Matsushima, Satoshi, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Meinel Aden and Marjorie, 1980-1982 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Memorials, Barrett Helen, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - McCarthy Martin S.J., 1978 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - McCarthy Martin S.J., 1978-1983 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Merrill Paul W., Correspondence, 1949-1951 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Mihalas Dimitri, Correspondence, Folder 1, 1984-1986 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Mihalas Dimitri, Correspondence, Folder 2, 1984-1986 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Mihalas Dimitri, Correspondence, Folder 3, 1975-1984 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Mihalas Dimitri, Letter, May 20, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Mihalas Dimitri, Letter to Truran re: Mihalas, November 13, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, undated (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - M-Z, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - M-N-O, 1953 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Nassau J.J., Correspondence, 1944-1956 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Nassau J.J., Correspondence, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Nassau J.J., Correspondence, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Nassau J.J., Correspondence, 1950 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Nassau J.J., Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Nassau J.J., Correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Sciences Correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 36, Folder 7-8)
  - O'Connell D.J. Father, 1974-1976 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Oort/IAU, 1947 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Oort Correspondence, 1953 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Oort-Lindblad, 1927-1970 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Osterbrock Donald E., 1979-1986 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Osterbrock Donald E., 1974-1980 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Palmer Patrick E., 1977 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Papers, 1962-1964 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Papers, Folder 1, 1955-1965 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Papers, Folder 2, 1955-1965 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Parker J. Reverend, Correspondence, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Perkins Barbara, 1974-1983 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1936 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1937 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1938 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1943 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1946 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1952 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1953 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1955 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1973-1990 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1973-1980 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Personal and Professional Correspondence, 1952-53 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Personal and Professional Correspondence, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Pontifical Academy of Science, Folder 1, 1977-1983 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Pontifical Academy of Science, Folder 2, 1974-1977 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - P-Q-R-S, 1952-1953 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Reynolds R.J., 1975-1976 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Ross Alan, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Rountree Lesh Janet, 1974-1981 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Sanner Fred, 1975-1979 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Schramm David N., 1981-1983 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Schwartz Marry W., Correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Schild R.E., 1984 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Shane C.D., Correspondence, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Sharpless Stewart, Correspondence, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Smith James, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Smith Malcolm G., 1975-1978 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Spinrad Hyron, 1976-1977 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Strumgren Bengt, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Struve Otto, 1946 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Struve Otto, 1949-1951 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Swings Pol, 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Treanor Patrick S.J., Letter, Aug. 24, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Treanor Patrick, S.J., 1977-1978 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - T-U-V, 1953 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - van Altena W.F., 1974-1982 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - van Biesbroeck Georges, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Van Den Bergh, Sidney 1975-1982 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Vandervoort Peter O., 1983 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Walborn, 1974-1980 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Whitford A.E., Correspondence, 1948-1952 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Whitford A.E., Correspondence, 1953 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Yale University, Maury Antonia Reminiscences, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - W-Z, 1952-1953 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Series III: Research
  This series contains most of the files related to Morgan's research in astronomy.
  Subseries 1 and 3 contain Morgan's research and observation notebooks and the tables and calculations he created. Spectra, Observation cards, Sky Maps, and general graphic material are grouped together in Subseries 2, "Graphic Material."
  Subseries 4, Research and Scholarly Writings includes research materials collected by Morgan, including papers by other scientists. Subseries 5, Publications contains notes, manuscripts and offprints of his own writings.
  - Subseries 1: Notebooks
    - Abell, undated (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Absolute Magnitudes, 1936 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Abt-Morgan, NGC 2516, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Atlas, undated (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Autumn, 1980, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - AWM Wak Cd Clusters, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - A0 - F2, 0h - 11h6.5m, undated (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - A0 - F2, 11h8m - 20h12, undated (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - A0 - F2, 20h13m - 23h59m, undatedG-Series (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - B Stars, also few O Stars, undated (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - B Variable Stars, 1926 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Bautz-Morgan, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Cepheid Color Program: W. Linke, undated (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Classification of Galaxies, Fall, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Classifications, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Clusters of Galaxies, 1964-1968 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Data for Luminosity Calibration, 1956 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Differential Equations II Problems, 1929 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - empty notebook, undated (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Fine Grain Development, 1935 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Final Form Classification, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Form Catalogue Final, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Further Investigations on MK-78 System - ζ, Cus Paper Beginning, 1979-1980 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Galactic Structure, 1962 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Galactic Structure, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Galaxies, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Galaxies, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Galaxy Classification Class, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - G-Series, undated (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - HD B8-A0 Bright Star Catalogue, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Hyades, Spec Results, 1964-1967 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Irregular Variables, 1928 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Low Surface Brightness Galaxies, 1963-1964 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Matthews - Morgan - Schmidt, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - McCormick Symposium, April, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - MK-70, 1968-1969 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - MKA System, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - MKHT, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - MKHT Spectral Atlas, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - MK System Revision, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - The Mk System of Spectral Classification, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Morgan Spectral Classification, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - W.W. Morgan Notebook, 1966-1967 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - NGC 2362, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Notes on Reflector Color Program, undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Nova Herculis, undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Observational Notebook 1, 1937-1941 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Observational Notebook 2, 1941-1943 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Observational Notebook 3, 1943-1946 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Observational Notebook 4, 1946-1947 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Observational Notebook 5, 1947-1948 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Observational Notebook 6, 1948-1949 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Observational Notebook 7, 1949-1950 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Observational Notebook 8, 1950-1951 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Observational Notebook 9, 1951-1954 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Observational Notebook 10, 1954-1957 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Observations, Notebook, F, undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Observations, Notebook, Δ, undated (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Observations, Notebook, "6 inch Reflector with 15 degrees" undated (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Observations, Notebook, 1929 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Observations, Notebook, 1932 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Observations, Notebook, 1945-1946 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Observations, Notebook, undated (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Observations, Notebook, undated (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Observations, Notebook, undated (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - On the Spectra and Forms of the Galaxies, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Orbit of ZZ Aurigae: Nova Cygni (1876), 1927-1928 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Paper III, July, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - P.C.K. Nebular Photometry: UV Series - Book 1, Contains Some TN and Other Series, Measures with Ross Photometer, 1932-1934 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Planetarium Address, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Preliminary Types, 10, undated (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Problems, 1936 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Programs, 1935 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Proceedings, Yerkes Astronomical Club, 1914-1916 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Proceedings, Yerkes Astronomical Club, Colloquia, 1916-1930 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Professional Notebook #16, undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Professional Notebook #17, undated (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Professional Notebook #18, undated (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Professional Notebook #19, undated 26 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Professional Notebook #20, undated 26 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Professional Notebook #21, undated 26 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Professional Notebook #22, undated 26b (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Professional Notebook #23, undated 26b (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Professional Notebook #24, undated 26b (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Professional Notebook #25, undated 26b (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Professional Notebook #26, undated 26b (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Professional Notebook #27, undated 26b (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Professional Notebook #28, undated 26b (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Professional Notebook #29, undated 26b (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Professional Notebook #30, undated (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Professional Notebook #31, undated (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Record, November, 1928 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Reference Notes for Variables: Moon, 1928 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - References, undated (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Revised MK Atlas for Stars Earlier than the Sun, 1975-1976 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Revised MK Atlas for Stars Earlier than the Sun, 1976-1977 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Revised MK Atlas for Stars Earlier than the Sun, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Revised MK Atlas for Stars Earlier than the Sun, 1977-1978 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Revised MK Atlas with Bright Stars in Orion Nebula, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Rome, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - J Russel Lecture, 1961 (Box 52, Folder 2-3)
    - RV Tauri Variables Novae, Hoffmeister's Variables, 1927 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Notebook: "Sections for Atlas Text," 1978 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Some Spectroscopic Phenomena Associated with the Evolution of Galaxies, 1958 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Spectral Intensity, undated (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Spectroscopic Investigations, 1981-1982 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Spectral Types, 1962-1967 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Spiral Arms, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Spiral Notebooks, F5, 1, 0h0m - 17h29m, undated (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Spiral Notebooks, F5, 2, 17h34m - 22h47m, undated (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Spiral Notebooks, F5, 2, 22h47m - 23h59m, undated (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Spiral Notebooks, F8-G5, 1, 0h0m - 5h51.2m, undated (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Spiral Notebooks, F8-G5, 2, 5h53.3m - 15h21.4m, undated (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Spiral Notebooks, F8-G5, 3, 14h21.6m - 21h40.8m, undated (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Spiral Notebooks, F8-G5, 4, 21h49.0m - 23h58.3m, undated (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Spiral Notebooks, K's, 1, 0h0m -5h55m, undated (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Spiral Notebooks, K's, 2, 5h58m-10h4m, undated (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Spiral Notebooks, K's, 3, 10h7m - 15h2.1m, undated (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Spiral Notebooks, K's, 4, 15h2.6m, 18h31.6m, undated (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Spiral Notebooks, K's, 5, 18h32.1m - 20h29.0m, undated (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Spiral Notebooks, K's, 6, 20h29.5m - 23h21.1m, undated (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Spiral Notebooks, K's, 7, 23h22.1m - 23h58.1m, undated (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Spiral Structure, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Star Catalog F8-K5, undated (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Stars Brighter than 5m, undated (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Stars Which Have No Cards, Vol. I, 1954 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Stars Which Have No Cards, Continuation of Vol. I, 1954 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Stellar Photometry: P.C. Keenan, 1934 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Stellar Populations, 1966-1967 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Summer, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Survey for Abt, 1971 27 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Survey for Abt, 1972-1976 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - TN Series - Book 1, Nebular Photometry, Ross Photometer, 1934 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Tucson, May, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Types: When?, Where?, What Plate Series?, Types by Whom?, Transcribed by Carrie?, undated (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Unlabeled, 1954 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Unlabeled, 1955 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Unlabeled, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Uppsala, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - UV Book 2 Series: Nebular Photometry, Measures with Ross Photometer, 1934 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Variables, 1928 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Variable Star Notes, 1927 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Variable Stars, January, 1927 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - X, Globular Clusters, 1959 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Y, May, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Alpha Per Cluster, 1970-1971 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Θ Series 6-inch Reflector, undated (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Δ Scuti and Metallic Line Stars with Sharp K Program, 1973-1975 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - ζ Cas Paper and Other Investigations, with Optical Forms of Galaxies in Spectral-Type Boxes, 1980-1981 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - 0 Associations: Catalogue of Star Clusters and Associations, Prague, 1958 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - 18-05 +86.6 6.8 out, 1934 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - 2 MK 0-B5, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 2: Graphic Documents
    - Abell 2199 = NGC 6166, 1965 10 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - A 545, undated (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - A 665, undated (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - An Attlas of Low-Dispersion Grating Stellar Spectra, 1967 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - An Atlas of Objective-Prism Spectra, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Basel Paper Illustrations, Folder I, undated, Folder12: Basel Paper Illustrations, Folder II, undated (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - BD Enlargement (Case), undated (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Betelgeuse, undated (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Burbridge Image Tube Camera Prints of Southern Radio Sources, Folder 1, undated (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Burbridge Image Tube Camera Prints of Southern Radio Sources, Folder 2, undated (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Burbidge NGC 4696: 60" Cevvu Tolulo Prints, 24" Michigan Schmidt, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Burbridge Plates, October, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Centaurus Association Prints - Burbidge CT 60-in, 103-a-0, 45m. See: Sersic: Atlas of Southern Galaxies pp. 66-67, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Cleveland, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Corbally Christopher J., Composite Spectra, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Cyg X1 Spectra, undated (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - DTM Kent Ford: Steam Star, undated (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Enlargements of Galaxies, undated (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Extra-Galactic Prints, No. 10, 11, 30, undated (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Finder Fields for Care Program, undated (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Galaxy Class, May 3, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Galaxy Form Classification, Original Maps, 1958 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Galaxy Form Classification, Original Maps, Folder 2, 1958 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Goldstein Mechanics etc., undated (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - HR 5401 Am Illustrations, undated (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - IC 2602 Illustrations, undated (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - IC 4296, Prints - Burbridge CT60in, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Images, Luminosity Effects at GO, 1976 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Illustration for Optical Forms of N Galaxies, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Keenan Letter, LMC F8-G8 Spectra: Scans of ζ Cas, HR 8752, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Kitt Peak, 10178, undated (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Lantern Slides: Keenan-McNeil Atlas, Plates 3, 4, 7, 8, 14, undated (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Light-Curves of Variable Stars, undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Luminosity Effects at 09, undated (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Lynds Spectra 4 COS34, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Main Sequence 09-B8, undated (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Spectral Enlargements, undated (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - MK Am Stars Figure 1 Revised, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - MK Chapter Illustrations, undated (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - MKAT H-J, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - MKAT Print Set A, undated (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - MKK 70 42, undated (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - MKK 70 42, Unknowns 1-20, undated (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - M.N. System, undated 10 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Morgan-Abt-Tapscott Figures, undated (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Morgan-Keenan Ama Rev. Illustrations, undated (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Morgan Spectral Classifications, 1-20, undated (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Morgan Spectral Classifications, Unknowns 1-20, undated (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Morgan Spectral Classifications, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Morgan, Stromgren, Johnson, ApJ 121, 611, Original Photographic Prints, 1955 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - A Morphological Life, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - New Aspects of Stellar Classification, undated (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - NGC 4154, Prints, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - NGC 5419 Prints - CT 60-in, 103-a-0: Burbidge - Burbidge, undated (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Objective: Prism Positives for Classification Class, undated (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Objective: Prism Positive for Student Classification, undated (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Observation cards Reference Guide, undated (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Observation cards, untitled, undated (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Observation cards and Lantern Slides, undated (Box 62)
    - Observation cards, Miscellaneous Cards, "Strogem Stars 1954", "O and B Stars, including those observed by Stebbuns, Haffer and Whitford for color, the OB stars from the Cleveland Program and the H O and B stars fainter than 5.50 and north of - 20°, 0h, 1h, 2h, 3h, 4h, and 5h", undated (Box 63)
    - Observation cards, "Observation cards for wide double stars to be observed photgraphically" (Two sets 1''-6'' and >6''), "Stars of all Types Brighter than 5.50 in BS Catalogue 0h, 1h, 2h, 3h, to -30°", "Miscellaneous", undated (Box 64)
    - Observation cards, "Stars of all Types Brighter than 5.50 in BS Catalogue 0h, 1h, 2h, 3h, 4h, 5h, 6h, 7h, 8h, 9h, 10h, 11h, 12h, 13h, 14h, 15h, 16h, to -30°" (Box 65)
    - Set 1: Observation cards, Brighter than 5.50 in BS Catalogue 7h, 8h, 9h, 10h, 11h, 12h, 13h, 14h, 15h, 16h, 17h, 18h, 19h, 20h, 21h, 22h, 23h, to -30°", undated (Box 66)
    - Set 2: Observation cards, Merrill HAlpha Stars 12h, 23h, undated (Box 66)
    - Observation cards, "R and N Type Stars", "O-B3 Stars", "High Velocity Stars < 7.0; Giants G5-M Between 6h and 16h", "Miscellaneous", "Dwarfs Fainter than 6.5, Stars of All Types Brighter than 5.50 in BS Catalogue, 4h, 5h, 6h", "B-Stars in Canis Major Region", undated (Box 67)
    - Observation cards, "B0, B1", "Stars Later than B5 having Corrected Apparent Magnitudes Brighter than 5.0", "B9p - A5p Stars", "S Type Stars", "Dwarf Stars", "Sub-Dwarfs and White Dwarfs", "O and B Stars: Including those Observed by Stebbius, Huffer, and Whitford for Color, the OB Stars from the Cleveland Program, and the HD O and B Stars Fainter than 5.50 and North of -20°, 6h - 17h", "O and B Stars: Including those Observed by Stebbius, Huffer, and Whitford for Color, the OB Stars from the Cleveland Program, and the HD O and B Stars Fainter than 5.50 and North of -20°, 20h", undated (Box 68)
    - Observation cards, "Double Stars", "Perseus Cluster Region II", "Merrill Stars", "B8 Stars in Orion Cluster Region", "O and B Stars: Including those Observed by Stebbius, Huffer, and Whitford for Color, the OB Stars from the Cleveland Program, and the HD O and B Stars Fainter than 5.50 and North of -20°, 18h", "O and B Stars: Including those Observed by Stebbius, Huffer, and Whitford for Color, the OB Stars from the Cleveland Program, and the HD O and B Stars Fainter than 5.50 and North of -20°, 21h, 22h, 23h", "Cluster Type Variables, Gaposchkin Variable Stars", "A0, A2, A3, A5, Aop; 11h, 12h, 13h, 14h, 15h, 16h, 17h", undated (Box 69)